<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Bloggie-McBlogface</title>
  <subtitle>A portfolio of sorts</subtitle>
  <link href="/bloggie-mcblogface/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/"/>
  <updated>2016-11-10T19:33:12.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Scott Gardiner</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#minus2</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/11/10/minus2/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/11/10/minus2/</id>
    <published>2016-11-10T19:13:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-11-10T19:33:12.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If the last month was slow, this one has flown by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sprint -2 and Sprint -1 complete.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Framework Upgrades in place for 2020 kicking off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tibco and Cucumber do not mix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debauchery, lies and hidden truths.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So scrap last month’s update. It was full of positivity and seeing the best in all things people related. That’s gone drastically downhill since then, as I have realised that things getting discussed at standup aren’t actually the full truth. Nobody has control of the overall endgame. It’s a power struggle with lots of people competing against each other in full blown silos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bigger silos than I’ve ever seen before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the plus side, it’s meant I’ve had plenty of time to focus on the Tibco stack, my own knowledge improving daily, and trying to integrate other functionality and systems with the current stack we have. Cucumber looks like a delightful thing, but it’ll mean SOAP to JSON conversions and manually building the payloads. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody wants that. It’ll be a pain in the arse to keep up to date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learnings: Though it may be possible, teamwork and breaking down silos isn’t easy. &lt;strong&gt;People do not like change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;If the last month was slow, this one has flown by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sprint -2 and Sprint -1 complete.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Framework Upgrades in place fo
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Project" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Project/"/>
    
      <category term="2020" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/2020/"/>
    
      <category term="Service" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Service/"/>
    
      <category term="Silo" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Silo/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#mdev</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/10/03/mdev/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/10/03/mdev/</id>
    <published>2016-10-03T09:41:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-10-03T10:12:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;2020 KTB is complete. It’s been a long month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holiday passed far too quick.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All Tibco 2020 work promoted to MDev &amp;amp; working.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SM VB dev completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been a busy month, full of teamwork from many different areas. 2020 has been completed, with a few hitches along the way - but we’re in and working. It’s been an experience with many ups and downs - from starting off with little knowledge of anything that’s going on and finding it hard to get any information, to seeing that it’s a project with several really promising ideas - and knowing how all the parts fit together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s quite compelling seeing so many different areas in a standup together and talking/working as a team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of working as a team, I feel like the Tibco team are working better together - It feels less broken. SL is starting to come out of her shell, and switching projects has given us a chance to appreciate what the others do. DM did some cool stuff with 2020 while I was away and it was nice to be able to come back and understand/add into what was done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a side note/project, I’ve completed a relatively small, but important piece of VBA for the SM team. It’ll reduce workload and a real pain point for managers completing the forms that are required. Hopefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risk have also asked me to pop in and talk to them about agile. Something I need to prepare for, as I’m by no means an expert. It’ll be a good stretch for me to try to get them to take some of the stuff we do on-board. Standups as a first measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learnings: Teamwork &amp;amp; non-silos across the business &lt;strong&gt;are&lt;/strong&gt; possible. It might just take a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;2020 KTB is complete. It’s been a long month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Holiday passed far too quick.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All Tibco 2020 work promoted to MDev &amp;a
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Project" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Project/"/>
    
      <category term="2020" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/2020/"/>
    
      <category term="Service" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Service/"/>
    
      <category term="Collaboration" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Collaboration/"/>
    
      <category term="Team" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Team/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#2020month</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/08/25/2020month/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/08/25/2020month/</id>
    <published>2016-08-25T19:23:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-10-03T10:22:40.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So a month has passed in the blink of an eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020 has commenced in service layer. With a bang.&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am the sole Tibco dev.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full development of all services required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of services with new tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tunnels within tunnels within tunnels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last 4 weeks has been a crazy blur. 2020 has taken over my life, caused me more political nightmares than I ever knew were possible and proved to me that I have a lot of skill with the tools I’m working with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My service layer is almost complete, built from scratch with very little help - this is my first large scale display of what I have achieved over the last year. And I have the small plus of people referring to me as the lead Tibco dev on the project. That felt good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new tools are both great and horrific in the same breath. They do some awesome things but can be horrible to talk to and get information from. I did enjoy being able to go back and make requests of other people though, made me feel like I’m gaining credibility with the other devs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tunnelling is my new favourite past-time. Or at least you’d think it is. It’s been a huge challenge to get my head around where I need to tunnel to and how tunnels even work. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My record so far is 9 tunnels at once. It’s not something I’m proud of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learnings: &lt;strong&gt;Don’t be afraid to put yourself forward and ask the difficult questions.&lt;/strong&gt; DP has proved that it can actually be very beneficial and people have listened to the request and given us a lot of information.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;So a month has passed in the blink of an eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020 has commenced in service layer. With a bang.&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am the sole Tibco 
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Project" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Project/"/>
    
      <category term="2020" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/2020/"/>
    
      <category term="Service" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Service/"/>
    
      <category term="Collaboration" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Collaboration/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#valued</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/07/25/valued/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/07/25/valued/</id>
    <published>2016-07-25T20:37:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-08-25T19:45:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been a long, slow couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Limit is essentially finished.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First solo standup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Values award nomination.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Credit Limit has been less of a challenge than I thought it would be (so far). I think I’ve learned more than I give myself credit for over the last 10 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not really an achievement, but I held my first mobile standup this week. It’s interesting to see that JJ is happy to give me that role before others who have been in the team longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DT arrived at my desk today and said that he’s putting me forward for a values award, which is awesome. Turns out that putting that much effort into getting to the hackathon was not only worth it, but seen from a distance as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;C2020 looks interesting. Last week was dipping my toes in the water and this week should see us start to get involved in the detail. It could be a huge project with a lot of work, or it could be a huge problem with a lot of work. Dependent on where the business decides to take it and the key architecture that’s implemented.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s going to be an interesting journey either way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also.. Pokemon go is ruining my life. But I love it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;It’s been a long, slow couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Credit Limit is essentially finished.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First solo standup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Values a
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Hackathon" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Hackathon/"/>
    
      <category term="Derek" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Derek/"/>
    
      <category term="Values" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Values/"/>
    
      <category term="Award" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Award/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#geekweek</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/07/11/geekweek/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/07/11/geekweek/</id>
    <published>2016-07-11T14:22:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-07-11T14:32:58.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Douglas has returned!&lt;br&gt;Not that there was much issue whilst he was off:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GI successful deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loans had one issue, which I found in the logs and pointed them in the right direction (not me!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PCA we don’t talk about, as they don’t know what they want. Twice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SSCA is an absolute monster, but I’m getting there. Slowly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hackathon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, a very successful couple of weeks. I have started creating the all important network that, until now, I had been shielded from. People have been coming to me with questions and I’ve been finding that I can answer them. Which I didn’t necessarily expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then the two weeks were capped off with the Hackathon. A great trip for Me, John, Mitesh, Megan and Jacob. First Hackathon, first podium finish. The idea of a garbage saver went down a treat, hooked into that all important loyalty system. Great feedback from the CTO, and I’m now intrigued to see if they take it on and make it happen.&lt;br&gt;Might pop the champagne cork winnings later..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learnings: I need to have more confidence in myself. The two times I asked for help, I got a terrible answer that I didn’t question. &lt;strong&gt;Must. Question. More.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, yeh.. and Pokemon go. It will ruin my life.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Douglas has returned!&lt;br&gt;Not that there was much issue whilst he was off:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GI successful deployment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loans had one i
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Hackathon" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Hackathon/"/>
    
      <category term="Grad" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Grad/"/>
    
      <category term="Group" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Group/"/>
    
      <category term="Plc" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Plc/"/>
    
      <category term="Achievement" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Achievement/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#longestweek</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/06/17/longestweek/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/06/17/longestweek/</id>
    <published>2016-06-17T15:20:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-06-21T15:36:50.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week has been a fruitful, if extremely long week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Factory 1 config is nearing completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, that’s all I’ve done. All week. From start to finish. Monday to Friday. ALL WEEK!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learnings:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copying a factory instance is not as easy as it sounds. (Don’t try it again - and if you do, be aware that there’s a lot of stuff you need to re-configure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jenkins allows for configurable builds, and you can carry variables through those builds for deployment purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The original SOAP tests that I wrote on my first service were awful, and I need to re-do them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SOAP has an option to add the same endpoint to all services, meaning I will waste no further time typing it in manually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you’re in the admin console, your build will not deploy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, it’s been a good week for learning. I now know what the build scripts actually do (and where they are failing silently), so I can go and amend them over the next couple of weeks. I really need to get to grips with Datagrid and deployments to SIT before Douglas goes away though.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;This week has been a fruitful, if extremely long week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Factory 1 config is nearing completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, that’s all
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Factory" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Factory/"/>
    
      <category term="Environment" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Environment/"/>
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Config" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Config/"/>
    
      <category term="Jenkins" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Jenkins/"/>
    
      <category term="Build" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Build/"/>
    
      <category term="Script" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Script/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#factory</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/06/13/factory/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/06/13/factory/</id>
    <published>2016-06-13T15:49:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-06-13T19:11:38.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The learning curve continues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean setup and config of new Continuous Integration Server (Factory1).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loans service completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update Money Transfer code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demo of JSON parsing for the rest of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning deployment processes for when Douglas is away.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Factory 1 setup has been an absolute beast. (Though I did spend a long time looking at port config, which has been resolved by the VPN I knew nothing about..). The re-config of Tibco machines and Jenkins integration is still being a pest, but I’m getting there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loans was a different challenge, but one that went really well. I feel like I’m getting a broader knowledge of the business as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JSON parse demo went really well -&lt;br&gt;The others gave me some food for thought and some tweaks I could make.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deployment processes seem…. interesting. There’s a lot of paperwork, and I need the full end to end process documented before Douglas leaves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, CB didn’t like my App idea that I submitted, so some thinking to do before next year.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;The learning curve continues:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean setup and config of new Continuous Integration Server (Factory1).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Loans service
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Factory" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Factory/"/>
    
      <category term="Environment" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Environment/"/>
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Config" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Config/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#holiday</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/18/holiday/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/18/holiday/</id>
    <published>2016-05-18T09:53:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-05-18T10:04:00.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week has been a learning curve of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSON handling PoC completed and stored for future use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RESTful service PoC completed for PCU and stored for future use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IA completed for a new loans service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IA completed for PCAO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IAs are not the easiest thing in the world - Basically trying to step through all the changes you need to make without actually completing them, and trying to foresee any issues this may cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The JSON handling is in a state where it works, as long as the order is specified - which isn’t really what JSON is about, so some refactoring to do there. (Or the potential purchase of a plugin to make it easier).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RESTful service is completed and ready to use / be adapted for future use in other projects - I think this will happen if we promote the fact that we can do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now for holiday - Bring on Portugal.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;This week has been a learning curve of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JSON handling PoC completed and stored for future use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RESTful servic
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="JSON" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/JSON/"/>
    
      <category term="REST" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/REST/"/>
    
      <category term="IA" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/IA/"/>
    
      <category term="Holiday" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Holiday/"/>
    
      <category term="Learning" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Learning/"/>
    
      <category term="PoC" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/PoC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#no</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/11/no/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/11/no/</id>
    <published>2016-05-11T15:41:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-05-11T15:59:19.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have said no. On multiple occasions. And nothing bad has come of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JobFamilies is complete and we’re not implementing top scrollbars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company-wide JobFamilies is not going to be made by us.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The SMF tool isn’t an option for us. We just don’t have time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Factory 2 mocks have had my life for several days, and I have admitted defeat; for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have finished my Qualys VBA coding and handed off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am looking at parsing JSON into Tibco, library imports and java are not playing easily, but I am trying to get a handle on it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tibco training went well, though I don’t feel I actually learnt much (The highlight was correcting the textbook).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have said no. On multiple occasions. And nothing bad has come of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JobFamili
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="Java" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Java/"/>
    
      <category term="PersonalDevelopment" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/PersonalDevelopment/"/>
    
      <category term="VBA" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/VBA/"/>
    
      <category term="Training" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Training/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#recap</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/02/recap/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/05/02/recap/</id>
    <published>2016-05-02T17:36:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-05-03T09:37:56.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;September to now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BAU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tibco integration bootcamp course in Rotterdam - &lt;a href=&quot;http://inter.viewcentral.com/events/cust/search_results.aspx?keyword=&amp;cat4_id=28&amp;eventMonthYear=&amp;event_id=23&amp;cat1_id=&amp;postingForm=default.aspx&amp;cid=tibco&amp;pid=1&amp;lid=5&amp;cart_currency_code=&amp;payment_type=&amp;orderby_location=&amp;orderby_date=&amp;newRegistration=&amp;bundle_location_group=&amp;errmsg=&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;external&quot;&gt;BW611&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;  Code in production:&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activate Card&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct Debit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logging &amp;amp; Error Upgrades&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JobFamilies project with the other Grads - &lt;a href=&quot;https://jobfamilies.tbdevops.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;external&quot;&gt;JobFamilies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RCSA improvements made, input form created for easier business usage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualys scripting work completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nominated by Derek for Chartered Banker: Young Banker of the Year 2016.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;September to now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BAU&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tibco integration bootcamp course in Rotterdam - &lt;a href=&quot;http://inter.viewcen
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Work" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/categories/Work/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Tibco" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/Tibco/"/>
    
      <category term="FirstPost" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/FirstPost/"/>
    
      <category term="BAU" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/BAU/"/>
    
      <category term="RCSA" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/RCSA/"/>
    
      <category term="YBOY" scheme="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/tags/YBOY/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>#blogstart</title>
    <link href="https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/04/29/blogstart/"/>
    <id>https://scottygar.co.uk/bloggie-mcblogface/2016/04/29/blogstart/</id>
    <published>2016-04-29T20:22:55.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-29T20:22:55.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
